<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>NiTEDREAM</title><description>A new creative media for Black digital cultures.</description><link>https://pandog.media/</link><item><title>Welcome (back (again?))</title><link>https://pandog.media/blog/welcome-back/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://pandog.media/blog/welcome-back/</guid><description>Guess who&apos;s back again (again).</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I had a massive revamp. Previously, this place was called Pandog Media and for 8 years, it served well enough. But after a while, I forgot why I chose that name and the logo didn&apos;t really work (even if the dog looked cute and I still have loads of stickers left).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s when I realised that I needed to rethink the whole brand, and its purpose (again). I knew it had to house all my projects and it still had to focus on Black cultures but what about the name? I remembered a book publisher called Grand Dreams from my childhood. The name fascinated me enough to stay in my head and that lead me to “daydream” (and an episode of Care Bears where a child—who I now know had ADHD—kept getting into trouble for daydreaming) but that was naturally taken in every form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what about &lt;em&gt;night&lt;/em&gt; dream? Or... nitedream? And then I thought about the SEGA Saturn game, NiGHTS into dreams and how that captivated me as a child. Everything&apos;s connected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And now NiTEDREAM is here. It&apos;s a collection of projects with a particular focus on Black expression of creativity. But it&apos;s always going to be a work in progress. Things could change but never so much as to go through another name change (please don&apos;t let someone have used this name already; I paid good money for this domain!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://bsky.app/profile/nitedre.am&quot;&gt;NiTEDREAM on Bluesky&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@nitedre.am&quot;&gt;hit me up&lt;/a&gt; if you want to leave a comment or work with me on something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then, sweet dreams!&lt;/p&gt;
</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>